{"cards": [
    {"front": "I want to eat sushi at eight o'clock.", 
     "back": "はちじに　すしを　たべたい。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "I will go to work by bike.", 
     "back": "わたしは　じてんしゃで　しごとに　いきます。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "I will go to the market now.", 
     "back": "わたしは　いま　マーケットに　いきます。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "This is a peach.", 
     "back": "これは ももです。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "This is not a peach.", 
     "back": "これは ももでは ありません。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "This is my book.", 
     "back": "これはわたしの　ほんです。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "I will go to Tokyo.", 
     "back": "わたしは　とうきょうへ　いきます。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "I bought a car.", 
     "back": "わたしは　くるまを　かいました。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "This is easy.", 
     "back": "これは　やすいです。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "This is tough.", 
     "back": "これは　じょうぶです。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "How much is this?", 
     "back": "これは　いくらですか。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "What is good?", 
     "back": "なにが　いいですか。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "I am writing a letter now.", 
     "back": "いま　てがみを　かいています。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "I want to eat tempura.", 
     "back": "てんぷらが　たべたいです。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "I wanted to eat tempura.", 
     "back": "てんぷらを　たべたがっていました。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "Please do not forget.", 
     "back": "わすれないで　ください。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "What do you do?", 
     "back": "あなたな　らどうしますか。",
     "type": "sentence"
    },
    {"front": "あ",
     "back": "ア",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "か",
     "back": "カ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "が",
     "back": "ガ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "さ",
     "back": "サ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ざ",
     "back": "ザ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "た",
     "back": "タ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "だ",
     "back": "ダ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "な",
     "back": "ナ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "は",
     "back": "ハ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ば",
     "back": "バ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ま",
     "back": "マ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "や",
     "back": "ヤ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ら",
     "back": "ラ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "わ",
     "back": "ワ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "い",
     "back": "イ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "き",
     "back": "キ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぎ",
     "back": "ギ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "し",
     "back": "シ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "じ",
     "back": "ジ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ち",
     "back": "チ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "に",
     "back": "ニ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ひ",
     "back": "ヒ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "び",
     "back": "ビ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぴ",
     "back": "ピ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "み",
     "back": "ミ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "り",
     "back": "リ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "う",
     "back": "ウ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "く",
     "back": "ク",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぐ",
     "back": "ヅ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "す",
     "back": "ス",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ず",
     "back": "ズ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "つ",
     "back": "ツ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぬ",
     "back": "ヌ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ふ",
     "back": "フ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぶ",
     "back": "ブ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぷ",
     "back": "プ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "む",
     "back": "ム",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ゆ",
     "back": "ユ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "る",
     "back": "ル",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "を",
     "back": "ヲ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "え",
     "back": "エ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "け",
     "back": "ケ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "げ",
     "back": "ゲ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "せ",
     "back": "セ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぜ",
     "back": "ゼ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "て",
     "back": "テ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "で",
     "back": "デ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ね",
     "back": "ネ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "へ",
     "back": "ヘ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "べ",
     "back": "ベ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぺ",
     "back": "ペ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "め",
     "back": "メ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "れ",
     "back": "レ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "お",
     "back": "オ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "こ",
     "back": "コ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ご",
     "back": "ゴ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "そ",
     "back": "ソ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぞ",
     "back": "ゾ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "と",
     "back": "ト",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ど",
     "back": "ド",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "の",
     "back": "ノ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ほ",
     "back": "ホ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぼ",
     "back": "ボ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぽ",
     "back": "ポ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "も",
     "back": "モ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "よ",
     "back": "ヨ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ろ",
     "back": "ロ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ん",
     "back": "ン",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "きゃ",
     "back": "キャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぎゃ",
     "back": "ギャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "しゃ",
     "back": "シャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "じゃ",
     "back": "ジャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ちゃ",
     "back": "チャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "にゃ",
     "back": "ニャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ひゃ",
     "back": "ヒャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "びゃ",
     "back": "ビャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぴゃ",
     "back": "ピャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "みゃ",
     "back": "ミャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "りゃ",
     "back": "リャ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "きゅ",
     "back": "キュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぎゅ",
     "back": "ギュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "しゅ",
     "back": "シュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "じゅ",
     "back": "ジュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ちゅ",
     "back": "チュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "にゅ",
     "back": "ニュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ひゅ",
     "back": "ヒュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "びゅ",
     "back": "ビュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぴゅ",
     "back": "ピュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "みゅ",
     "back": "ミュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "りゅ",
     "back": "リュ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "きょ",
     "back": "キョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぎょ",
     "back": "ギョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "しょ",
     "back": "ショ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "じょ",
     "back": "ジョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ちょ",
     "back": "チョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "にょ",
     "back": "ニョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ひょ",
     "back": "ヒョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "びょ",
     "back": "ビョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "ぴょ",
     "back": "ピョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "みょ",
     "back": "ミョ",
     "type": "kana"
    },
    {"front": "りょ",
     "back": "リョ",
     "type": "kana"
    }
]
}
